music
There are eight planets
in our solar system
We all revolve around the sun
Join us to learn about the different planets
Now sing along and have some fun
My name is Mercury
I'm the second hottest
planet
The closest one to the sun
A year on my surface is
88 days
I'm the smallest
but I'm lots of fun
My name is Venus
I'm the hottest planet
But the second planet
from the sun
I'm the brightest planet
in our solar system
And I'm
too hot for anyone
My name is Earth
I'm the planet you live on
The third Planet from the sun
I'm the only planet
with organic life
So take
care of me because we're all one
My name is Mars
I am red in color
I'm
the fourth planet from the sun
I have the highest mountain
in our solar system
A volcan
o named Olympus Mons
There are eight planets in our solar system
We all revolve around the sun
Join us to
learn about the different planets
Now sing along
and have some fun
My name is Jupiter
I am covered in clouds. I'm the fifth planet from
the sun
My giant red spot is
a raging storm
As for size
I'm the biggest one
My name is Saturn
I am brown in color
I'm the sixth planet from the sun
My outer rings are extremely
thin They're made
of dust and icy chunks
My names Uranus I am blue in color
I'm the seventh planet from the sun
Humans have named me the
icy planet
Because I am the coldest one
My name is Neptune
I am blue in color
I'm the eighth planet
from the sun
I have too many
storms in my atmosphere
And I'm
the furthest planet from the sun
There are eight planets
in our solar system
We all revolve
around the sun
Join us to learn
about the different planets
Now sing along and have some fun